<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
    <Recipe id="P-7444" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-7736" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Method:
        1.Weigh quinoa into 4&quot; hotel pan
        2.wash and drain
        3.add water or veg stock
        4. place in steamer and steam 20 mintues
        5. once cooked fork wrap and place in warmer for service

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9714" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
        TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny,

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingredients
        2.wash and cut to size required
        3.place in container, label and store in fridge

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Gather all ingredients and tools
        2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9851" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
        TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-13933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
        TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-15353" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Dump beer into large cambro
        2. Slowly pour in dry ingredients while mixing with wooden spoon or gloved hand to avoid lumping but being
        careful to not develop gluten too much- LESS MIXING=MORE FLUFFY BATTER
        It may appear a little too thick at first, a small amount of fizzy water helps, but after a 30 minute proofing
        period/letting it sit in the fridge it will bubble up to perfection
        3. Lable &amp; rest in fridge for 1/2 hour beore use to proof

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning: beer and fizzy water arn&apos;t reflected in the recipe.

        Utensils needed:


        -
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-18318" image="">1) Thinly slice up green onion.

        2) Place in apropriate sized conatianer, label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny,

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingredients
        2.wash and cut to size wanted
        3.place in container, label and store

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

        n/a

        Icon:

        vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

        Method:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-20368" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. gather ingredients
        2. cut Chard into strips
        3. wash and dry
        4. place in contain label and fridge
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

        2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26019" image="">1. Combine well</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
        2. Mix in garlic
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26021" image="">1) Rinse quinoa in hotel pan under cold water while agitating quinoa until the water
        from the pan runs clear

        2) Place rinsed quinoa to hotel pan, with appropriate amount of water and steam until cooked, around 40 minutes.

        4) Spread out on baking tray, carve gridlines to allow quinoa to cool more quickly. Cool in fridge, store in
        appropriate vessel. Label, date, refrigerate
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26055" image="">1. Put liquid egg in hotel pan and put in rationale oven on 100% steam for 10-15
        minutes, or until the egg have cooked, but are still slightly creamy.

        2. Add to vessel. Add fresh herbs, seasoning and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26057" image="">1. Pre heaet grill to 350F/medium heaet

        2. Spread oil on grill and allow to get hot

        3. Crack egg on oil, allow whites and yolk to set. Season with salt &amp; pepper for sunny side up egg

        4. Gently flip over and cook for 15 - 30 seconds for over easy egg
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26058" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine lemon juice, salt and pepper in jug of vitamix

        2. Slowly pour in canola oil to emulsify

        3. Put in appropriate container, label, date and refrigerate

        4. Alternatively, fill up a squeeze bottle 1/3rd of the way with lemon juice, a pinch of salt and pepper, and
        the rest with romano oil. Shake it.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice.

        2. Puree jalapenos in robot coupe until finely minced.

        3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice.
        Mix well.

        3. Adjust seasoning.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26069" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. In mixing bowl, combine arugula, citrus dressing, salt &amp; pepper mix.

        2. Mix to lightly dress arugula.

        3. ONLY MIX WHAT YOU NEED. THIS DOES NOT HOLD WELL.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26076" image="">1. Combine onion, bay leaf and cloves in cheese cloth, tie up tight.

        2. Place milk and cheese cloth bundle in large sauce pot. Bring to a simmer, then turn off heat. Allow to infuse
        for 10 minutes

        3. Remove cheese cloth bundle. Keep warm

        4. Add butter to clean sauce rondeau. Melt butter until it starts generating bubbles, cook until bubbles stop
        and water is cooked out.

        5. Take butter off heat and add flour, a little at a time until smooth and white roux forms.

        6. Add milk while still off heat a little at a time being sure to incorporate, well, with whisk before adding
        more milk.

        7. Add bechamel back into medium low heat until it simmers. Allow to simmer, stirring frequently with spatula
        (ensure to scrape bottom, the flour loves to stick to the bottom of the pan!) for 15-20 minutes.

        8. Add salt &amp; pepper mix, parm, havarti and mozzarella. Stir well until evenly incorporated.

        9. Allow to cool in appropriate vessel. Label, date and refrigerate
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26090" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink.
        Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs
        clear

        2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice
        and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

        3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date,
        refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26136" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Prepare pickling liquid as per recipe

        2. Add red onions.

        3. Allow to pickle 24 hours if possible.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26140" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Method:
        1.Preheat oven to 400*F
        2.In large mixing bowl, combine tomatillos, poblanos, jalapenos, garlic, oil and S+P. Mix well to coat.
        3.Place cooling rack over med high flame on burners. Roast tomatillos, peppers and onions until charred all
        over. Place on baking tray. Add garlic.
        4.Roast until peppers, onions and tomatillos are cooked through and soft enough to blitz in food processor,
        about 10-15 minutes.
        5.In bowl of food processor, add roasted vegetables, cilantro leaves and stems, lime juice and salt. Process
        until a unalagos consistency.

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26164" image="">1) Crush fennel seeds and mustard seeds coarsely.

        2) Combine all, mixing very thoroughly.

        3) Transfer to appropriate vessel, label and date and store in dry storage area.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1) In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high
        heat. Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot. Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not
        overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown. Taste for seasoning.

        2) Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26216" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1.place a strainer in the kettle. If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone. If you can&apos;t find
        it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

        2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the
        water to a FULL boil.

        3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not
        stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
        APPROX 7 MINUTES

        4. Drain water and stir in lots of ice, stirring constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled be sure
        to drain any excess water. Then add oil and stir

        5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26226" image="">1) In large rondeau over medium-lowheat, add oil. When oil is warm, add garlic and fry
        until garlic is golden brown. Ensure to cook garlic until it is no longer bitter to taste. Add chili flakes and
        fry for about 30 seconds - 1 minute more.

        2) Add crushed tomatoes and bring to a simmer. Add seasoning and simmer 5 minutes more. Take off heat.

        3) Add tomato sauce to appropriate vessel and puree with immersion blender until smooth. Label, date,
        refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26229" image="">1) In large pot, bring water and salt to a boil

        2) bring water down to a simmer and gently cook lasagna noodles, being careful not to rip or tear.

        3) Strain noodles, allow to cool slightly and add oil to ensure that noodles will not stick together.

        4) reserve for lasagna, or store in appropriate vessel and label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26311" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) In a large stock pot, add water and vegetables.

        2) Bring to a simmer and allow to simmer for 30-40 minutes. Carefully strain stock through fine chinoise and
        store in appropriate vessel.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26378" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. With 1/4 inch dice attachment on the robocope dice shallots and then tomatoes (so the shallots don&apos;t get
        stuck/lost make sure they are processed first), place in perferated hotel pan and let drain excess liquid out
        for 10-15 minutes.

        2. Add diced tomato and shallot and mix with puree garlic, chiffonade basil, olive oil, balsamic vinegar and S&amp;P
        in mixing bowl and mix throughly. Taste for seasoning.

        3. Check quality after 24 hours.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26380" image="">1) Preheat oven to 300F.

        2) Put almonds in oven, toast for 10 minutes. Rotate pan and stiralmonds and toast for another 5 minutes or
        until golden brown. Allow to cool.


        Allergens:

        Nuts/Treenuts
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26381" image="">1) Preheat oven to 200*F

        2) Combine all in large sauce pot. Bring to a very gentle simmer (just until you can see small bubbles forming
        rapidly)

        3) Put pot in oven for 3 hours. Strain, reserving garlic. Transfer to appropriate storing vessel and allow to
        cool.

        4) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26382" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:
        PLEASE NOTE CUT SIZE ON SWEET POTATOES IS 1/4&quot;

        1. Preheat oven to 425*F

        2. In a mixing bowl add yam, zucchini, red peppers, garlic, jalepenos, red onion, corn, chili oil and UBC house
        rub. Mix well.

        3. Put hash on baking tray or roasting pan in an even layer (DO NOT OVERCROWD PAN OR YOU WILL STEAM THE VEG
        RATHER THAN ROAST).

        4. Roast for 15-20 minutes, or until sweet potato is caramelized and cooked through. Remove from oven and let
        cool.

        5. Once cooled add hash to a large mixing bowl and combine with drained black beans, cilantro and mix well.

        6. Check seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26383" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine lime juice, mustard, garlic, cumin, and S&amp;P in jug of vitamix. Blend well.

        2. Slowly pour in oil over medium speed to create an emulsification.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26390" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine water and salt in a large pot. Bring to a boil.

        2. Add buskwheat soba to boiling water, then turn heat down to medium and simmer noodles until tender but not
        overcooked, about 2 mins. TASTE FOR AL DENTE

        3. *Drain noodles well and ensure to rinse very, very well under cold running water, gently agitating by hand.
        This will ensure that the noodles will not overcook, and will not be sticky when stored.

        4. Mix well with sesame oil once cooled and hold for service.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26393" image="">1) Preheat deep fryer to 350*F

        2) Remove baskets from deep fryer. Ensur to have a mixing bowl and tray lined with papertowels, and a spider.

        3) Place two large handfuls of julienned tortilla strips in hot oil. Deep fry for 45s - 1 minute, or until
        tortillas are cooked through and very crispy.

        4) Retrieve with spider and drain excess oil. Season with salt in mixing bowl and place on papertowel lined pan.

        5) Place in appropriate container once cooled. Label, date, and store in a cool dry place.

        Allergens:

        Gluten
        Wheat
        soy (from tortilla)
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26401" image="">

        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Preheat deepfryer to 350*F

        2. Drain and dry chick peas very well.

        3. Fry the chickpeas in the hot oil.

        4. Place crispy chickpeas in mixing bowl and season with chickpea spice.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26459" image="">1) Spread some tomato sauce on the bottom of a 2&quot; hotel pan.
        -Add oven ready lasagna noodles to cover.

        -Add vegetable mixture to cover.

        -Add layer of noodles then more tomato sauce.

        -Add noodles then cheese sauce.

        -Repeat until hotel pan is nearly full.

        2) Top off layers with mozza. Wrap tightly.

        3) Bake in a 375*F oven for 30-45 minutes.

        Uncover and bake until sauce is bubbling and cheese is melted and brown. minutes or so.

        4) Hold for service.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26481" image="">The below looks like old info to me that req&apos;s a rework- to revisit. 3496279


        1) Put eggs in perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for predetermined time.
        (2 step program)
        1 - 100% steam 147*F Preheat
        2 - 100% Steam 147*F 45 minutes. Turn on alarm notification.

        2) Load eggs and cook for program cycle.

        3) Upon receiving order from customer, simply add egg to hot water for 1 minute to reheat egg and carefully
        crack egg onto dish. Serve immediately.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
        2. Cut stem off
        3. Pick leaves off

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26527" image="">1) Place beets in perforated tray. Steam beets until tender enough that a paring knife
        can be easily inserted into beet with little resistance. Allow to cool. When cool enough to handle, slip off
        skins and cut into bite sized portions.

        2) Season with salt and pepper and store in appropriate vessel.

        3) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-27273" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Avocado Taost.jpg">1) Grill or toast
        ciabatta until crisp and warm.

        2) Sread evenly with guacamole, than top with bruscetta mix, arugula then pickled onions.

        3) Garnish with hemp hearts.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-27275" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Black Bean Bowl.jpg">1) Combine Quinoa with half of cumin lime
        dressing, place in bowl.

        2) In a saute pan over medium heat, add oil. Once hot, add potato hash and dressing and sauce until warm
        throughout, about 1 minute. Drop poached egg into warm water.

        3) Add chopped cilantro to hash and plate on top of warm quinoa. Place avocado on top of hash, make a well for
        the egg and put egg in. Garnish with more cilantro and serve.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-27405" image="">1) Combine warm brown rice or quinoa and sweet potato hash with 30 ml of cumin lime
        dressing and season well. Place in serving bowl.

        2) Top with tomatillo salsa, pico de gaillo, crispy corn tortilla strips, avocado, jalapeno slices and lime
        wedge.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-28396" image="">serve in the indicated proportions
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-28989" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in: SAUCE|Mayo|Vegan

        Method:

        1) Drain chick peas through strainer. Retain chick peas fir recipe or use.

        2) This will yeild 1L of aquafaba to keep for recipes if needed, if not discard.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-31957" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-32459" image="">Allergens:

        Sulphite
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-32739" image="">1) Chill can of coconut milk in fridge for 24 hours. Ensure to store upside down.

        2) Chill bowl of stand mixer in fridge for an hour, or stick lots of ice and cold water in it to chill.

        3) Open can of coconut milk and scoop out fat and discard coconut water.

        4) Place the sugar in the mixing bowl of the standmixer

        5) Beat until fluffy and smooth with stand mixer with whisk attachment. Add vanilla and whisk some more to
        incorporate.

        6) Store in appropriate container. Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-32800" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Drain chickpeas, lightly mash into a course texture using a food processor. Do not blend into a smooth paste.

        2. Add green onion, red pepper, cilantro, vegan mayo, garlic, ginger, turmeric, lemon juice and salt and pepper
        into chick peas. Mix well to combine.

        3. Adjust seasonong.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-32809" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine all well.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-32886" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Curried chick pea.jpg">1. Place appropriate amount of quinoa or
        brown rice in mixing bowl. Dress with cumin lime dressing, mix well and place in serving bowl.

        2. Top with chickpea salad portion, papadum crackers and crispy chickpeas.

        3. Place chutney in corner of bowl. Garnish with lemon wedge (1/6th of a lemon- please remove ALL seeds).
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-33555" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Chop pickles and set aside pickel juice
        2.Chop parsely very fine with a sharp knife
        3. Mix all ingredients in mixer and fully incorperate
        4. Season with lemon, L&amp;P sauce, salt and pepper to taste
        5. Store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:NA

        Utensils needed:Cutting board bowl whisk scale container
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-33557" image="">1) Combine all well.</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-35255" image="">1) Cut cucumber in quarters lenght wise, cut out seads.

        2) Cut remaining pieces in to 1.5 inch lenght pieces and cut in to 1/16th inch sticks.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-35258" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
        2. Using the robocoupe attachement to slice 1/8&quot;
        3.

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed: insert, robocoupe
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-35733" image="">PREP RECIPE
        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1) Toast nori by waving it over grill until it crisps up on both sides. Allow to cool.

        2) Combine half of the sesame seeds, sugar and salt in jug of vitamix blender. Blend well until combined into a
        paste. Do not over process or you will be making sesame paste, and that isn&apos;t very good.

        3) Crumble up nori very finely in vitamix. Combine ground sesame mixture, crumbled nori, and remaining sesame
        seeds and korean chili flakes.

        cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-38515" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 3/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how
        to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice celery to 3/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41468" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:
        pickle|onion red

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine and boil to dissolve sugar and bring flavours out of spices and seasonings.

        2. Strain liquid before pouring over ingredient to be pickled and allow time to work its magic.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-42425" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
        2. Slice cucumber to 1/8 thinkness
        3.

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed: robocoupe
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43719" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine all well. Put in fridge overnight to allow oats to soak up liquid. Combine with other
        fruits/garnishes as indicated in recipes.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43737" image="">1) Bring water to a rapid boil in an appropriate sized pot. Gently lower eggs into
        boiling water with a slotted spoon.

        2) Cover pot with aluminum foil and turn heat off completely. Allow eggs to sit in hot water for 8-9 minutes.

        3) Strain eggs, and shock in ice bath to stop eggs from cooking further and to make them easier to peel.

        4) When eggs are completly cool, peel them.

        5) Egg whites should be fully cooked, and yolk should be slightly runny.

        6) Store in appropriate contianer. Label, date, refrigerate.

        Allergens:

        Egg

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-43738" image="">1) Prep soba noodles as per recipe, and portion.

        2) Prepare Dobanjiang Sauce as per recipe.

        3) Place chilled soba noodles in mixing bowl and mix well with dobanjiang sauce. Place noodles in serving bowl
        and garnish with remaining vegetables. Zigzag a squirt of sauce on top of vegetables, then garnish with sesame
        and nori and soft boiled egg. Cut the egg in half and present the cut side.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43918" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        ***This recipe does not need to be heated, put all of the ingredients in a bowl and whisk well.***

        1. Combine all well.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1) Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment. If you don&apos;t know
        how, ask chef or a 1st cook.

        2) Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

        3) Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

        Allergens:

        No known prioirity allergens.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44475" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
        2. Set up robot coupe slicer for 1/8&quot; slicing. If you don&apos;t know how to set it up, ask Chef or a 1st
        Cook.
        3. Chop the ends off of jalapenos and place in compost bin. Do not remove seeds. Set up 4&quot; full hotel pan
        under the chute to catch the sliced jalapenos.
        4. On the slowest speed, carfully drop peppers into the feed chute. Do not mash a whole bunch in there, or else
        the cuts won&apos;t come out even.
        5. Repeat until production is done for the day. Label, date, refrigerate, or hold cold for service.

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44652" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
        TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44675" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        JOhnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44728" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny

        Products related to this Prep recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1.gather igredients
        2.chop leaves
        3.wash and dry
        4.label and fridge

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-44779" image="">THIS IS A PRODUCT RECIPE, final product handed to the customer...


        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. fry 13 pieces / 1LB to order
        2. when fully crispy put in bowl with sauce in container on side
        3.Serve.

        Portioning:13 peices = 1lb wings 60ml sauce

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingedients
        2.pick leaves
        3.place in container, label and store in fridge
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:

        Allergen:

        n/a

        Icon:

        n/a

        Method:

        remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Gather all ingredients.

        2. Remove peels and pits from avocados.

        3. Put all ingredients in a bowl and mash them together until fully combined trying to keep the avocado as
        chunky as possile

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44964" image="">1) Remove kale leaves from the tough woody stem by tearing or running a knife along
        the stem to remove leaves.

        2) Discard stem and process kale as dicated by recipe.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-45062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Method:
        1.Combine ingredents up to 3 days in advance.
        -store, label and rotate

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-45118" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingredients
        2.steam beets in steamer till soft
        3.peel under water once cool enough
        4.cut into pieces and toss with remaining ingredients
        5. spread on roasting pan
        6. Roast 200C/400F 15 minute or till done
        7.Hot hold in insert for service covered
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:130g

        Utensils needed:cutting board steamer pan roasting pan
        serving dish

        Allergen:

        n/a

        Icon:

        vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

        Method:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-45231" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-46869" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Neatly dice the Shallots in Brunoise size
        2.Save the trimming for stock
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, storage container

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-46870" image="">Allergens:

        none
        Icons:

        n/a

        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE
        WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Method:

        1.zest the most outer layer of the lemon using a fine microplane
        2. Set aside zested lemon to be used first/ juiced
        3. Use zest as close to recipe execution as possible but any excess is to be Stored, labeled and rotated
        correctly with any older product diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-48487" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine tomatoes, chile de arbol, garlic cloves. Add water until vegetables are just covered.

        2) Bring to boil, turn down to a simmer and continue simmering until tomatoes are soft, about 10-15 minutes.

        3) Remove vegetables by straining into a large bowl. ENSURE TO RESERVE WATER!

        4) Add vegetables to a vita mix, or puree with hand blender in an appropriatly sized vessle. Puree until smooth,
        but do not strain. Add some reserved water if you are having difficulties pureeing, or if puree is too thick.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-48488" image="">
        1) Warm tortilla shell on the flat-top grill with a small amount of oil. Grill until warm and slightly crispy.

        2) Meawhile add more oil to the grill and fry the egg.

        3) Spread refried beans on tortilla shell and place fried egg on top of beans.

        4) Top with warm Rancheros Salsa, and add mozzarella cheese, and top with chopped cilantro. Serve immediately.


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-48494" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingredients scale out ingredients
        2.chop cilantro
        3.mix into sauce
        4. Place in container label fridge
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:NA

        Utensils needed:Cutting board scale bowl whisk container
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-49663" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Steam beets until fork tender.

        2. Peel and chop into cubes.

        3. Combine all ingredients in food processor.

        4. Pulse until combined and smooth texture.

        5. Remove from mixer, adjust seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

        2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue
        this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent
        bruising.

        3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

        *Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50464" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU**

        Related Products this prep gets used in:
        Mac &amp; cheese

        Method:

        1) Set milk out to warm up while doing other steps.

        2) In pot melt the butter over medium heat

        3) Add the flour through fine mesh chinois while whisking melted butter to insure that no lumps are formed.

        4) Stir until the mixture is smooth and with out lumps, this is the time to be more careful. Cook for 1 minute
        so the flour becomes tastier and absorbs the fats. The roux should be a nice golden colour.

        5) Add warm milk to roux in a steady stream, whisking continuously. Simmer on low heat until it starts to
        thicken, but insure it does not come to a boil. Whisk in the salt and pepper mix, and nutmeg, taste for
        seasoning and adjust if needed. Set aside for recipe.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50500" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

        2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a
        tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

        3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they
        do not last very long.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-50555" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Omelet.jpg">1. Preheat flat top 350*F.

        2. In one side of the flat top. Add oil, vegetables and salt Cook about 2 minutes.

        3. In the other side of the flat top. Pour the liquid egg. Once egg starts to set add the sauteed vegetables and
        cheese and folder over.

        4. Garnish with chopped parsly and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50583" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1. Gather All ingredients
        2. Chopped capers to desire size
        3. Store in container

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed: Cutting Board, knife, storage container
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50584" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1. Gather all ingredients
        2. Chopped to desired size
        3. Store in appropriate container, label and fridge

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed: cutting board, knife, storage container
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1. Gather all ingredients and tools

        2. core out stem

        3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

        4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50636" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Chef Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens

        Method:

        1. Gather all Tools and ingredients
        2.
        3.

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently


        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50689" image="">Saute zucchini and season.</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50801" image="">1.In a 350F pre-heated oven.
        2. Lay flat pumpkin seeds on a sheet pan.
        3.Roast pumkin seeds for 5-8minutes or until turns a bit brown but not burnt.
        4. Take it off from oven.
        5. Let it cool and transfer to a dry container.
        6. Store in a dry place until needed.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50966" image="">Template to Cut + Paste into OC Preps:

        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Wash Tomato in cold water
        2.Cut in half Lenght wise
        3.Container label fridge
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
        knife, cutting board, storage container
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-51230" image="">This Recipe is a RATIO


        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-51988" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Method:
        1.Toss chicken wings in bredding.
        2.Lay out on baking sheets single layer.
        3.Bake at 375f till internal temp reachs 72c.
        -Cool, store, label and rotate this item witholder product correctly and dillgently

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53081" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Place all ingredients into food processor or blender and puree on high speed until smooth creamy texture.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-53084" image="">Dress bun top and bottom with tahini dressing.

        Place cooked burger on bottom bun.

        Top with smashed avocado.

        Top with citrus arugula.

        Close bun, secure with pick.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53126" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Warm bechamel over medium heat, stirring often to ensure sauce doesn&apos;t scald on the bottom of the pot.

        2. Have shredded cheese ready and add off the heat while stirring to melt.

        3. Adjust seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. make a tasty vegetable stock
        2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53336" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1. Cut stem of jalapenos and chop
        2. Sautee all except vinaiger for 5 min
        3.Add vinaiger, simmer and reduce the vinaiger by about half
        4. Blend until very smooth

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53339" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Warm veg stock.

        2. Mix spices well and mix into dry couscous.

        3. Pour hot stock over couscous and cover with cling film. Wait 10 minutes.

        4. Remove film, add, diced peppers, oil &amp; lemon juice and using a fork stir well to break apart all the
        grains of cous cous.

        5. Add herbs and stir.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53341" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Place all ingredients EXCEPT oil into Cambro/ Vitamix.

        2. Blend and slowly add oil in a steady stream.

        3. Adjust seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-53342" image="">1. Warm pita on flattop and cut into 3 equal pieces..

        2. Spread hummus onto the side of the large bowl.

        3. Place couscous in bottom of bowl.

        4. Dress spinach, cucumbers and tomatoes in dressing and place in one side of bowl.

        5. Place falafel next to vegetables, then cut pita with points facing up and top with hemp seeds and lemon
        wedge.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1. Gather all ingredients and tools
        2. Cut stem off
        3. Give a rough chop and keep the seeds

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-54697" image="">
        PREP RECIPE

        There are approx. 4 lemons per pound. a lemon is cut into 8 wedges, this recipe represents this.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55098" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Gluten
        Wheat
        Soy

        Method:

        1. Make overnight oats as per recipe.

        2. Combine remaining ingredients (EXCEPT OATS) in a large cambro container and blend well with immersion
        blender. Mix well into overnight oats and let stand in the fridge overnight.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-55117" image="">1) Place oats in bowl.

        2) Top with sliced banana, coconut cream &amp; toasted almonds.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55127" image="">1) In Robot Coupe slice onion and zucchini.

        2) In Robot Coupe shred carrots.

        3) Drain roasted peppers and slice.

        4) In rondo over medium heat add olive oil and seasoning. Add onion, garlic and carrot and sweat until softened
        and fragrant.

        5) Add zucchini and peppers and cook until just warmed through (3-4 minutes).

        6) Check for seasoning.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-55133" image="">1. Spread ingredients evenly inside the tortilla, fold in half and grill on the flat
        top, ensuring both sides are golden brown and crispy.

        2. Cut into 4 even pieces.

        3. Place tortilla strips on plate and put quesadilla on top to prevent the bottom getting soggy.

        4. Garnish on the side of the plate with salsa and sour cream.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55134" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. In rondo add oil, onions, peppers and salt/ pepper and sweat until softened and fragrant.

        2. Remove from heat and add spinach to wilt.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55548" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Cut corn tortillas in thin strips.

        2. Fry WITHOUT baskets, and use spider to drain well from oil.

        3. Season as soon as tortillas come out of oil as salt will NOT stick once they are cool.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-55819" image="">THIS IS A PRODUCT RECIPE, final product handed to the customer...

        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Place crispy seasoned fries into conatiner first, then freshly cooked crispy pieces of fish on top of fries

        2.sauce and lemon placed near the edger so sauce doesnt fall over
        3. ask if the custopmer wants ketchup, mayo, salt&amp;pepper or vineagar with thweir order


        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56398" image="">
        BEFORE COMMITING TO COOKING THIS RECIPE; GATHER ALL INGREDIENTS, UTENSILS REQUIRED AND READ METHOD THOROGHULY!

        1.Small dice pickled jalapenos and tomatoes. mince cilantro.

        2. in a bowl combine all ingredents. mix well keeping chunks visible in the mixture. check for seasoning.

        3. Ready to use or store in apropriate size cambro with serano wrap directly contacting the surface of the guac
        as well as a lid on the container (to stop oxidization)

        LABEL/DATE/REFRIGERATE
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56500" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1. Cook pasta to al dente. This is very important as the pasta will soak up the sauce and get very soft/ mushy
        if it is over cooked.

        2. Drain pasta well and mix with sauce.

        3. Adjust seasoning.

        4. Top with mozzarella and parmesan and bake in a 350F oven for ??? minutes ensuring top is golden brown and
        pasta is hot..

        5. Makes 16 portions (2 x 8).

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56509" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Breakfast Quesadilla.jpg">1. Place
        tortilla on flattop, spread cheese evenly on both sides (this will be the glue to hold the whole thing together.

        2. Add remaining ingredients evenly over the entire surface so each bite gives you all the ingredients..

        3. Fold in half and cook on both sides until golden brown and crispy.

        4. Cut into 4 even pieces. Place crispy tortilla strips on plate and place quesadilla on top to prevent bottom
        from getting soggy.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56696" image="">1. On flattop make omelet.

        2. Warm mushrooms and at the last minute mix w/ pesto.

        3. Place mushrooms in the middle of omelet, sprinkle cheese and fold shut.

        4. Serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56797" image="">1) Place shallots in food processor, making sure not to over fill.

        2) Puree until desired consistency is achieved.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56921" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. core the pepper composting craps
        2. cool, store, label, wrap and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56923" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Remove timatillios hood and compost as trim
        2. toss lightly in oil and salt + pepper
        3. roast at 250 for 25 minutes
        4. cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-57097" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Add oil to large rondo or saute pan.

        2. Over medium heat sweat shallots, garlic and chili flakes, rosemary until fragrant (1-2 minutes).

        3. Add chopped kale and toss to combine and wilt adding a few drops of water if needed to prevent burning.

        4. Cool mixture completly then add cooked white beans, mix well.

        5. Season to taste.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-57098" image="">1. Spread ingredients evenly inside the tortilla, fold in half and grill on the flat
        top, ensuring both sides are golden brown and crispy.

        2. Cut into 4 even pieces.

        3. Place tortilla strips on plate and put quesadilla on top to prevent the bottom getting soggy.

        4. Garnish on the side of the plate with salsa and sour cream.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-58348" image="">current price per lb is $2.50. 1 CT = 8 lb of pumpkin

        Average yield for whole pumpkin to peeled seeded raw pumpkin is approx 65%

        Method:
        - peel &amp; seed the pumpkin
        - place in container, label, date.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-58350" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Heat olive oil in large saucepan or Dutch oven over medium heat, add onion and pinch of sea salt and sauté
        until onions are soft and tender (about 5-8 minutes) stirring frequently.

        2. Add garlic and saute for additional 3 minutes, add the pumpkin puree, tomato sauce, sugar, and water stirring
        to combine, turn the heat to low and simmer for 10 minutes.

        3. Add the coconut milk, cinnamon, rosemary, sage and stir to combine, simmer for 5 minutes, add sea salt and
        cracked black pepper to taste.

        4. Add the cooked pasta &amp; roasted pumpkin and stir to combine.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-58351" image="">Method:
        - heat pasta sauce in frying pan, or hold hot in bain marie
        - add hot pasta, chopped swiss chard, cinnamon, 1/2 rosemary, salt &amp; pepper and stir until chard has just
        wilted
        - add 1/2 of the pumpkin pieces &amp; tomato and toss together.
        - place pasta in appropriate service dish, top with remaining pumpkin, tomato
        - garnish with pumpkin seeds, toasted coconut, remaining rosemary &amp; sage
        - serve
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-58353" image="">Method:
        - spread coconut ribbons on parchment lined sheetpan
        - Toast in oven ( low fan ) at 375f until golden
        - remove from oven, allow to cool
        - label &amp; date
        - hold for service

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-58355" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        Approx 20% yield loss due to cooking pumpkin.

        1. Cut pumpkin into 5cm chunks ( approx size ).

        2. Fine chop the rosemary.

        3. Toss the pumpkin with olive oil, salt, pepper, rosemary and maple syrup.

        4. Spread out in even layer on a sheet pan lined with parchment.

        5. Roast in a 400f oven until soft, lightly caramelized. (should be able to mash with a fork)

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-58738" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1. Gather all ingredients

        2. Zest lemons, Mince parsley

        3. Lighltly toast Panko till slightly golden.

        4. Once panko is cool fold all ingredents together and reserve for garnish.


        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-60548" image="">THE RECIPE IS A PREP, an in house made ingredient recipe
        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. pat fish dry
        2. fully coat fish in batter letting excess batter fall off before deep frying
        3.slowly drop into deep fryer using a slow &apos;wave&apos; motion to cook one side and make that side float
        before dropping it gently in
        4. ensure that fish isnt sticking to fryer basket
        5. Let fish cook to a golden brown colour and pull basket up to drain for at least 90 seconds before seasoning
        6. Transfer fully cooked fish to a bowl and season with salt and


        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-60550" image="C:\Users\johnnyb\Desktop\food truck OK mac n cheese.png">THIS IS A PRODUCT RECIPE, final
        product handed to the customer..

        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-61253" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Place beets in a food processor, pulse 2-3 times. DO NOT puree, there needs to be texture for the patties to
        hold together.

        2. Fine dice onion.

        3. Transfer beets to a large bowl, add other ingredients and stir to combine. If texture is too mushy, add more
        bread crumbs until desired consistancy. NOTE the bread crumbs and quinoa will slowly absorb excess moisture over
        time.

        4. Scale and shape burgers and place them on a parchment lined baking sheet.

        5. Bake patties in oven for 15 min, flip over and bake for a further 15 min. Hold for service OR

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:
        patty portion weight 160 grams

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
</Recipes>
